Welcome back.
We're here to tell you today, what you should wear, and other items that you need to have, when you work out on the elliptical trainer.
The first thing that you really need to have, is something that's loose, comfortable fitting. Nothing that's binding. You don't want your knees to get caught.
You want to feel very comfortable in what you're wearing.
Comfortable shoes is a must.
Something that you can tie, and that wouldn't slip off very easily.
Something to have a little room, just as if you're running, and when you're working on the cardio machine, your feet can swell slightly, so it's best to have very comfortable fitting shoes, is a very important thing, because the grips on the shoes, would be on the pedals and you want to feel safe, and be able to really feel free to move on the machine, so if you have very good, comfortable shoes, it's really important.
You'll also need a towel, because you're going to sweat.
That's what you need to do today, is you need to really let this go, and let it sweat.
Sweat it out.
This is what it's about, working your heart, and so having a towel, is a must.
You'll need that to feel good, and to keep the gym clean, of course too, but you also will need water.
You're going to replenish that sweat, so you have to drink, and you'll be able to really feel the recovery then, when you have the water, and you hydrate yourself, so that's why it's most important to go ahead, and have these items, for that safety reasons.
The other thing that you really need to have, I think is so important, is a proper type of music.
Some gyms play their own music, which can work very nicely for yourself, if you like that type of music, but you can personalize it by just bringing your own headphones, and having the only type of music that you like, and the rhythms, and the things that you like to listen to, which will help you to move more freely, and enjoy your experience on the elliptical trainer, so thank you, and we'll be right back.